One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Big News
Büyük Haberler
Pangaea Castle Mary Geoise
Pangaea Kalesi Mary Geoise
The World Conference, also known as the Reverie...
Reverie olarak da bilinen Dünya Konferansı;
is a grand assembly of fifty kings and queens
Dünya Hükûmeti'ne bağlı...
that represents over 170 countries affiliated with the World Government.
170'ten fazla ülkeyi temsil eden elli kral ve kraliçenin katıldığı büyük bir toplantıdır.
It is held every four years.
Her dört yılda bir tekrarlanır.
As always, the Reverie concluded in a state of great confusion
Her zamanki gibi Reverie yine büyük bir kargaşayla bitti...
and all the representatives returned home.
ve tüm temsilciler evlerine geri döndü.
Then...
Ardından...
one week later...
Bir hafta sonra...
Good grief... I'm finally home.
Şükürler olsun ki sonunda evime döndüm.
Ryugu Palace, Ryugu Kingdom Fishman Island
Balıkadam Adası, Ryugu Krallığı Ryugu Sarayı
Truly, the surface world is so far above us.
Sahiden, yukarıdaki dünya bizden çok uzak.
Um, thank you so much for escorting us,
Bize eşlik ettiğiniz için size çok teşekkür ederiz...
Sir Luffy's grandfather!
Luffy-sama'nın dedesi!
It was a pretty long trip, huh, Neptune?
Epey uzun bir yolculuk oldu ha, Neptune?
You must be tired!
Yorulmuş olmalısın!
I'm exhausted.
Öldüm, bittim.
Garp, stay here with us and replenish your energy.
Garp, bizimle kal da biraz dinlenip kendine gel.
Well, maybe I'll have a cup of tea,
Eh, bir çayınızı içeyim o zaman...
but considering the situation, I can't stay here for long.
ama vaziyet ortada, pek kalamam buralarda.
The Reverie always triggers big incidents.
Reverie hep büyük olaylara gebedir.
When fifty countries gather, a simple "let's get along" won't suffice.
Elli ülke toplandığında işler öyle sadece "anlaşalım" demekle bitmiyor.
Each of them has their own internal troubles.
Her birinin kendi iç meseleleri var.
Large and mighty countries just stare quietly at each other
Büyük devletler sessizce birbirini süzerken...
and let their proxies bicker.
aradaki küçükleri didişmeye bırakıyorlar.
They use resources and technologies as leverage.
Ellerindeki kaynakları ve teknolojiyi göz korkutmak için kullanıyorlar.
They say that all countries are on equal footing, but that's just talk.
Tüm ülkelerin eşit olduğu savunuluyor ama sadece lafta.
Wealth, poverty, and religious differences won't allow them to be equal.
Zenginlik ve inanç ayrılıkları varken asla eşit olamazlar!
Even if they appear to shake hands and smile, they'll gladly step on each other's feet.
El sıkışıp gülerler ama arkadan birbirlerinin kuyusunu seve seve kazarlar.
I wonder how many leaders can speak for both their citizens and those of other countries.
Kendi halkı kadar başkalarını da düşünen kaç lider kalmıştır ki?
It's only a roundtable in name.
Kıçımın yuvarlak masası...
You're right. Conversations among the sovereigns were touch and go.
Haklısın. Hükümdarlar arasındaki görüşmeler pamuk ipliğine bağlıydı.
We're no exception, but quarrels between countries can't be solved so easily.
Biz de istisna değiliz ama ülkeler arasındaki çekişmeler öyle kolay çözülmüyor.
The further a country's history extends,
Bir ülkenin tarihi ne kadar eskiyse,
the deeper the roots of its conflict will grow.
anlaşmazlığın kökleri de o kadar derine iner.
Even if there is a disagreement, as long as no blood is spilled, I call it peace.
Anlaşmazlık olsa bile kan dökülmediği sürece ben bu duruma barış derim.
But what happened this time was pretty bad...
Ama bu sefer yaşananlar felaketti!
This may be coming a bit late, but there's one thing I haven't told you about yet.
Biraz geç oldu ama size henüz bahsetmediğim bir şey daha var.
Right after the Reverie was dismissed and we set off, an incident occurred,
Reverie dağılıp yola çıktığımızda, bir hadise vuku buldu.
I received a report while aboard our ship.
Raporu ben gemideyken ilettiler.
We Marines will do our best to resolve it, but please don't fear
Biz Denizciler bunu çözmek için elimizden geleni yapacağız,
the surface world or us humans!
ama lütfen yüzeyden ve biz insanlardan korkmayın!
An incident...?
Ne oldu?
Garp, what kind of report did you receive?
Garp, nasıl bir rapor aldın?
The incident concerns the Kingdom of Alabasta.
Alabasta Krallığı'nı ilgilendiren bir olay.
The Kingdom of Alabasta...
Alabasta Krallığı...
Princess Vivi!
Vivi-sama!
Before all of this transpired...
Tüm bunlar yaşanmadan önce,
At the World Economic News, right after the Reverie was dismissed...
tam Reverie bittiği sırada Dünya Ekonomi Gazetesi'nde...
Unbelievable! It's incident after incident!
İnanılmaz! Ardı ardına şeyler yaşanıyor!
I can't believe so much happened at once...
Bir anda nasıl bu kadar çok şey oldu anlayamıyorum.
Listen up! Find me the greatest headline yet!
Dinleyin! Bana şimdiye kadarki en harika manşeti bulun!
Sir, which one should make the front page?!
Efendim, hangi haberi ön sayfaya basalım?
Listen! We have a death on our hands!
Dinleyin! Elimizde bir ölüm haberi var!
Editor-in-Chief Morgans World Economic Newspaper
Dünya Ekonomi Gazetesi Genel Yayın Yönetmeni, Morgans
Big obituaries move papers!
Büyük ölüm haberleri çok gazete sattırıyor.
Then, the headli–
O hâlde başla–
No, wait!
Hayır, bekle!
The resolution they passed is also good.
Toplantının sonucu da uyar gibi!
But a murder attempt is exciting as well!
Suikast girişimi de dikkatleri çekebilir!
That's right!
Çok doğru!
Okay, let's have two front pages!
Ön sayfada iki tanesini paylaşacağız!
The back page will have the same format!
Arka sayfa da aynı formatta olacak!
– Okay!
– Anlaşıldı!
Sir.
Efendim!
Express mail from the government.
Hükûmetten acil posta geldi!
A check, huh?
Bir çek, ha?
Oh, that's a lot!
Oh, bayağı iyimiş!
I see. It's an order to manipulate information.
Demek öyle... Haberi çarpıtmamızı istiyorlar!
But for which affair?
Ama neden ki?
Hushing up this incident?!
Bu olayı gizlemek için ne bu acele?!
No way in hell!
Hayatta olmaz!
Throw this back in their faces!
Çeki götlerine soksunlar!
Hey, what's wrong?
Hey, sorun ne?
My, my, my...
Hayır, hayır, hayır...
Do as you're told, Morgans!
Sana söyleneni yapacaksın, Morgans!
The secret agency,
Gizli teşkilat...
Cipher Pol?!
Cipher Pol mu?!
You must obey orders from the World Government.
Dünya Hükûmeti'nin emirlerine uymak zorundasınız.
Don't move!
Kıpırdama!
Never underestimate Big News Morgans!
Büyük Haberler Morgans'ı asla küçümsemeyin!
When did he sneak in?
Bu ne ara içeri sızdı?
Sir! Members of Cipher Pol are government officials!
Efendim! Cipher Pol üyeleri hükûmet yetkilileridir!
I know!
Biliyorum!
It's dangerous to stay here, guys.
Burası artık tehlikeli, millet.
Let's fly!
Hadi uçalım!
I may be avaricious,
Hırslı olabilirim...
but I am first and foremost a journalist!
ama her şeyden önce bir gazeteciyim!
I make people dance to the tune of my lies.
Yalanlarımla insanların kalpleriyle oynarım.
I'm a DJ of words!
Kelimelerin uzmanıyımdır!
I decide what to publish!
Neyin yayınlanacağına ben karar veririm!
Mr. Morgans!
Morgans-san!
You have a call from King Wapol!
Kral Wapol'dan bir çağrı aldık!
King Wapol?
Kral Wapol mu?
What does he want?
Ne istiyormuş?
Well, it sounds like he has information to leak.
Görünüşe göre sızdırılacak bilgileri var.
What?!
Ne?!
What's going on?
Neler oluyor?
A special report?
Özel baskı mı?
Don't worry...
Endişelenme...
It'll be all right.
Her şey iyi olacak.
With the government's failure to hush up what had happened,
Hükûmet olanları örtbas edemeyince,
the decisions the leaders made at the Reverie, as well as the incidents that occurred there,
Reverie'deki hadiseler ve kararlar...
instantly became known throughout the world and left many people in shock.
tüm dünyada duyulup büyük şok yarattı.
Vayyt!
Bekle!
Vhaat the hell is this?!
Bu da ne böyle?!
Revolutionary Army Headquarters Kamabakka Queendom
Kamabakka Kraliçeliği Devrim Ordusu Karargâhı
This cannot be true!
Bu doğru olamaz.
It is just a story in the paper, right?
Uydurma bir haber olmalı, değil mi?
That is just the WEN! Their bird president must have written nonsense!
Şu Ekonomi Gazetesi işte! O kuş başkan uydurmuştur!
I am sure of it!
Bundan eminim!
This is Sabo after all!
Sabo'dan bahsediyoruz!
It just cannot be...
Bu imkânsız!
I do not buy it!
Buna asla inanmam!
Calm down!
Sakin ol!
First, we must confirm the facts.
Öncelikle bu söylenenleri doğrulamamız gerekiyor.
But with all of them out of contact...
Ama hepsiyle iletişimi kaybettik...
how can we confirm?
nasıl teyit edebiliriz ki?
It's not true, is it?
Bu doğru olamaz, değil mi?
Sabo...
Sabo-kun...
Royal Escort Ship Kingdom of Goa
Goa Krallığı Kraliyet Koruma Gemisi
My lady!
Leydim!
He was in Mary Geoise?!
Mary Geoise'de miydi?!
M-My brother?!
K-Kardeşim orada mıydı?!
Windmill Village Kingdom of Goa
Goa Krallığı- Yeldeğirmeni Köyü
What happened to Makino?
Makino'ya ne oldu?
The bar is closed today.
Bar bugün kapalı.
What?!
Ne?!
So much has happened in the world...
Dünyada çok fazla şey oluyorken...
I could use a drink.
bir içki iyi giderdi.
Sabo is...
Sabo-kun...
Mt. Colubo Kingdom of Goa
Goa Krallığı- Colubo Dağı
And I had just learned he was still alive...
Tam da hayatta olduğunu yeni yeni öğrenmişken...
Tell me it's not true!
Gerçek olmadığını söyle bana!
Sabo!
Sabo!
Undersea Prison Impel Down
Sualtı Hapishanesi- Impel Down
I never get bored with this world!
Bu dünyada sıkılman imkânsız!
It's getting interesting!
İşler ilginçleşiyor!
Hey, guys!
Hey, millet!
Beehive Pirate Island
Korsan Adası- Hachinosu (Arı Kovanı)
Let's set sail!
Haydi yelken açalım!
Instead of watching the Marines snatch it away,
Onu denizcilere vermektense...
I'll take it for myself!
kendim alırım daha iyi!
And now, we return to the present...
Ve şimdi, günümüze dönelim.
The Outskirts of Ebisu Town Wano
Wano- Ebisu'nun Dışı
Koby, it's me.
Koby, benim.
Present Day A Stretch of Open Sea
Günümüz Denizde Bir Yerde
Hold on a second.
Bekle bi' saniye.
Let me go somewhere private.
Daha sakin bir yere geçeyim.
Okay.
Tamam.
Oh, yeah! Sea!
Ah, doğru! "Deniz!"
Fog!
"Sis!"
As always,
Her zamanki gibi...
you're a stickler.
dikkatlisin.
Well, it is a rule...
Şey, kural kuraldır...
Oh, right! It's terrible!
Ah, evet! Dinleyin!
There's something I need to report to you,
Size acilen bildirmem gereken bir konu var,
Commander!
Komutan!
X Drake Marine Headquarters Officer of SWORD, a Top Secret Special Force
X Drake Denizci Karargâhı Çok Gizli Özel Birlik SWORD Subayı
What?!
Ne?!
That's the situation?!
Demek vaziyet bu?!
Yeah. Even with all the Marines in the world
Evet. Bütün Denizciler birleşse bile...
it's too much to handle.
bunu temizlemek imkânsız olacak.
Captain Koby Marine Headquarters Member of SWORD
Denizci Karargâhı Tümamirali ve SWORD Üyesi Koby
So just as we planned,
Yani planladığımız gibi,
the Marines won't get involved with what's going on over there.
Denizciler oradaki mevzuya müdahale edemeyecek.
They don't have enough manpower.
Ellerinde yeterince adam yok.
That's fine.
Sorun yok.
Wano isn't affiliated with the World Government.
Wano, Dünya Hükûmeti bünyesinde değil.
Now, about Big Mom arriving at Onigashima...
Şimdi, Big Mom'ın Onigashima'ya gelmesi hakkında...
Yes.
Evet.
Kaido and Big Mom have been at odds for so long
Kaido ve Big Mom'ın ezeli düşmanlığı,
that the Marines are hoping those two pirates will ruin each other.
Denizciler için birbirlerini yok etmeleri adına bir fırsattı.
Yeah, I guess.
Evet, öyle.
As we expected, Kaido and Big Mom were at each other's throats...
Birbirlerini yok etmelerini beklerken,
but now they've joined hands!
el ele verip ittifak kurdular!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What do you mean?!
N-N-N-Nasıl yani?!
As for Straw Hat Luffy, there's been no word of a breakout.
Hasır Şapkalı Luffy'ye gelince, kaçtığına dair bir haber yok.
The situation is at a standstill.
Çıkmaza girdik.
There's also one more unpleasant thing.
Bir de şu can sıkıcı mesele var...
I saw Cipher Pol 0 in the capital the other day.
Geçen gün başkentte Cipher Pol 0'ı gördüm.
What?! Why are they in Wano?!
Ne?! Neden Wano'dalar?!
I hope I'm wrong,
Umarım yanılıyorumdur...
but it must mean the World Government
ama bu, Dünya Hükûmeti'nin...
is doing business with Wano, a country ruled by a pirate.
korsanlar tarafından yönetilen Wano'yla iş yaptığı anlamına gelir.
When I found out,
Bunu öğrendiğimde...
I was stunned for a few minutes.
bir süre kendime gelemedim.
By the way, where are you now?
Bu arada, sen neredesin?
Right.
Evet.
We're heading toward the Isle of Women...
Boa Hancock'u yakalamak için...
to capture Pirate Empress Boa Hancock!
Kadınlar Adası'na doğru gidiyoruz!
Oh, my...
Olamaz...
Those ships coming toward us over the Calm Belt...
Şu gemiler Calm Belt'den geliyorlar.
Is that a Marine fleet?!
Denizci filosu mu?!
Marguerite!
Marguerite!
What's going to happen?!
Neler oluyor?!
The news spread all around the world.
Haberler tüm dünyaya yayıldı.
They should have done this a long time ago!
Bunu çok daha önce yapacaklardı!
It was a mistake to team up with pirates...
Korsanlarla takım olmaya çalışmak bir hataydı!
They're evil!
Onlar şeytan!
For those who think all pirates are bad...
Tüm korsanların kötü olduğunu düşünenler...
Those government dogs will finally go away!
Sonunda şu hükûmet köpeklerinden kurtuluyoruz!
Screw that Pirate Empress, Hawk Eye, and Clown!
O İmparatoriçe'nin de Şahin Göz'ün de Palyaço'nun da canı cehenneme!
They're nothing but looters!
Onlar yağmacıdan başka bir şey değil!
...and for those who hate looters, it's good news.
...ve yağmacılardan iğrenenler için müjde bir haber bu!
But I thought they did great in the Summit War!
Ama Zirve Savaşı'nda hepsi harikaydı!
That's what they decided?!
Reverie'nin kararı bu muymuş?
The Marines are ready to take immediate action.
Denizciler derhal harekete geçmeye hazır.
Is this really wise?
Akıllıca bir iş mi bu?
They were one of the world's three great powers!
Onlar dünyanın en büyük 3 gücünden biri!
For those who knew of their feats in the Summit War,
Zirve Savaşı'ndaki başarılarını bilenler...
and those who were concerned about disrupting the balance of the three great powers,
ve üç büyük gücün dengesinin bozulmasından endişe duyanlar için...
it was truly an alarming situation.
bu gerçekten sıkıntılı bir durumdu.
The news story from the latest Reverie that stunned people across the world the most...
Son Reverie'den gelen ve tüm dünyayı şoke eden...
was...
o haber...
the abolition...
Shichibukai sisteminin...
of the Seven Warlords system!
kaldırılmasıydı!
The Seven Warlords of the Sea were pirates officially recognized by the government.
Shichibukai, hükûmetin resmen tanıdığı korsanlardı.
While they were allowed to pillage,
Yağma yapmalarına izin verilse de...
the government used them as deterrents against other pirates.
hükûmet onları diğer korsanlara karşı caydırıcı olarak kullanıyordu.
The roster of the Seven Warlords has changed over time.
Shichibukai kadrosu zaman içinde defalarca değişime uğradı.
Crocodile.
Crocodile.
He clashed with the Straw Hats over the Kingdom of Alabasta.
Alabasta Krallığı'nı ele geçirmeye çalışırken Hasır Şapkalarla çatıştı.
He was trying to take over the kingdom
Krallığı devirmeye çalışsa da...
but was ultimately defeated by Luffy and expelled from the Seven Warlords.
en sonunda Luffy'ye yenildi ve Shichibukai'den ihraç edildi.
The man who replaced Crocodile and joined the Seven Warlords...
Crocodile'ın yerine geçen ve Shichibukai'ye katılan isim...
was Marshall D. Teach.
Marshall D. Teach'ti.
However, he announced his resignation after achieving his goal.
Ancak amacına ulaştıktan hemen sonra istifasını sundu.
Jinbe, Knight of the Sea,
Denizin Şövalyesi Jinbe...
opposed the Summit War and grew disdainful of the Marines.
Zirve Savaşı'na karşı çıktı ve Denizciler'le arası bozuldu.
He, too, declared his resignation.
O da istifasını ilan etti.
Gecko Moria.
Gecko Moria.
This man who had once clashed with the Straw Hats was also called to the Summit War.
Hasır Şapkalarla bir zamanlar çatışan bu adam da Zirve Savaşı'na çağrılmıştı.
However...
Ancak...
just after the war, an order for an ambush came from high up in the government,
savaşın hemen ardından hükûmet emriyle pusuya düşürüldü...
and he was expelled.
ve sistemden atıldı.
Heavenly Demon Donquixote Doflamingo.
Gökçe Şeytan Donquixote Doflamingo.
All while governing Dressrosa as its king,
Dressrosa'yı kral olarak yönetirken...
he trafficked an artificial devil fruit, SMILE, as an influential underground broker.
yeraltı dünyasının kilit ismi olarak yapay şeytan meyvesi "GÜLÜCÜK" ticareti yapıyordu.
However...
Ancak...
he lost the kingdom in a struggle against Luffy's alliance,
Luffy'nin ittifakına karşı krallığı kaybetti...
and his title of Warlord was revoked.
ve Shichibukai unvanı elinden alındı.
And finally, Trafalgar Law.
Ve son olarak, Trafalgar Law.
He allied himself with the Straw Hats to take down Doflamingo...
Doflamingo'yu devirmek için Hasır Şapkalarla ittifak kurdu...
and was stripped of his title.
ve unvanından oldu.
The four pirates who reign supreme as if they're emperors:
Adeta birer imparator gibi hüküm süren dört korsan:
the Four Emperors.
Yonko.
And trying to contain them: Marine Headquarters.
Onları dizginlemeye çalışan: Denizciler.
Last but not least: The Seven Warlords of the Sea.
Ve son olarak: Shichibukai.
The Seven Warlords of the Sea
Shichibukai
These three great powers have kept the world at peace.
Bu üç büyük güç, dünyadaki barışı muhafaza ediyordu.
The Four Emperors Navy
Yonko Denizciler
However,
Ancak...
two kings had suffered terribly at the hands of Warlords:
Shichibukai yüzünden büyük acılar çeken iki kral vardı:
King Nefertari Cobra of the Kingdom of Alabasta,
Alabasta Krallığı'ndan Nefertari Cobra...
and Riku Doldo III of the Kingdom of Dressrosa.
ve Dressrosa Krallığı'ndan 3. Riku Doldo.
They fought for the abolition of the Seven Warlords system.
Shichibukai sistemini tamamen yıkmak için mücadele ettiler.
Then, after a heated debate at the Reverie,
Ve Reverie'deki hararetli tartışmaların ardından...
a large majority supported the proposition, and it passed.
teklif oy çokluğuyla kabul edildi!
Therefore, the Seven Warlords of the Sea will automatically be stripped of all their rights,
Dolayısıyla, Shichibukai üyeleri tüm haklarından otomatikman mahrum bırakılacak...
and their connection with the World Government will hereby be cut off.
ve Dünya Hükûmeti ile olan tüm bağları bundan böyle kesilecektir.
That means...!
Bunun anlamı...
Empty Bluffs Island New World
Yeni Dünya Karai Bari Adası
Buggy,
Buggy,
you're just another pirate!
artık sadece sıradan bir korsansın!
That's no fair, you assholes!
Bu hiç adil değil, sizi adi herifler!
A decision was made without telling us, and since we're no longer useful, you arrest us?!
Bize sormadan karar alıp, işiniz bitince de bizi tutuklamaya mı kalkıyorsunuz?!
You have no sense of justice whatsoever!
Sizde zerre adalet duygusu yok!
Whether Crocodile and Doflamingo outsmarted you is none of my business!
Crocodile ve Doflamingo'nun sizi parmağında oynatmasının benimle hiçbir ilgisi yok!
Don't take it out on me!
Acısını benden çıkarmayın!
They've got the whole coast surrounded!
Bütün kıyıyı kuşatmışlar!
What should we do?
Ne yapacağız şimdi?
My entire life's plan is going to the dogs!
Hayatımın planı mahvoldu, her şey bitti!
Oh?
Ha?
An Island in the New World
Yeni Dünya Bir Ada
The Marines should be on our side, but they've surrounded us!
Denizciler bizim tarafımızda olmalıydı ama bize karşı duruyorlar!
What should we do, Mommy?!
Ne yapacağız anneciğim?!
Mommy!
Anne!
The Ruins of the Muggy Kingdom Gloom Island
Kuraigana Adası Shikkearu Krallığının Kalıntıları
Surrender yourself now,
Teslim ol,
Hawk Eye Mihawk!
Şahin Göz Mihawk!
Surrender yourself now!
Hemen teslim ol!
The Isle of Women Amazon Lily
Kadınlar Adası Amazon Lily
Snyake Princess, we have a problem!
Yılan Prenses, başımız dertte!
Your title of Warlord has been stripped away!
Shichibukai unvanınız elinizden alındı!
Elder Nyon!
Nyon-sama!
There are Marine ships off the coast!
Kıyılarımızda Denizciler cirit atıyor!
What?!
Ne?!
They've already gone into action?!
Çoktan harekete mi geçmişler?!
Don't panic!
Panik yapmayın!
Snyake Princess!
Yılan Prenses!
They've obviously forgotten something...
Belli ki bir şeyi unutmuşlar...
don't you think?
değil mi?
This is no good, President Buggy!
Bu hiç iyi değil, Başkan Buggy!
Should we run?!
Kaçmalı mıyız?!
Of course not! We'll show them a flashy fight!
Tabii ki hayır! Onlara gösterişli bir savaş sunacağız!
Show some guts, you sad sacks!
Biraz cesur olun, sizi pısırıklar!
– That's our President Buggy!
– İşte Başkan Buggy'miz!
Former Warlord of the Sea
Eski Shichibukai
Buggy's Delivery Chairman Buggy "the Bombastic Clown"
"Gösterişli Palyaço" Buggy
Buggy's Delivery Chairman Buggy "the Bombastic Clown"
Buggy Sevkiyat Başkanı "Gösterişli Palyaço" Buggy
– Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
– Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
Former Warlord of the Sea
"Gösterişli Palyaço" Buggy
Seems like they're not on our side anymore!
Görünüşe bakılırsa artık aynı tarafta değiliz!
How incredibly unforgivable...
Bu gerçekten affedilemez...
Weevil!
Weevil!
You have permission to take them down!
Onları yok etmene izin veriyorum!
R-Really?!
G-Gerçekten mi?!
In that case, I'm gonna kill 'em...
O hâlde hepsini öldüreceğim!
Edward "Whitebeard Jr. (Self-Proclaimed)" Weevil Former Warlord of the Sea
Edward Weevil (Kendince "Küçük Beyazsakal") Eski Shichibukai
in the name of Whitebeard!
Tabii Beyazsakal adına!
I feel a tremor of excitement.
İçim kıpır kıpır.
It's been a long time...
Uzun zaman olmuştu...
Dracule Mihawk "Hawk Eye" Former Warlord of the Sea
"Şahin Göz" Dracule Mihawk Eski Shichibukai
Former Warlord
Eski
Dracule Mihawk
Dracule Mihawk
"Hawk Eye" Former Warlord of the Sea
"Şahin Göz" Dracule Mihawk Eski Shichibukai
since I was the one being hunted.
avlanan taraf olmayalı.
Dracule Mihawk "Hawk Eye" Former Warlord of the Sea
"Şahin Göz" Dracule Mihawk Eski Shichibukai
We became the Seven Warlords of the Sea...
Bizler Shichibukai unvanını...
"Pirate Empress" Boa Hancock Former Warlord of the Sea
"Korsan İmparatoriçesi" Boa Hancock Eski Shichibukai
Former Warlord of the Sea "Pirate Empress" Boa Hancock
Eski Shichibukai "Korsan İmparatoriçesi" Boa Hancock
because of our might!
çok güçlü olduğumuz için aldık!
I'm counting on you guys.
Size güveniyorum beyler!
In the meantime...
Siz onları oyalarken...
I'll get the hell out of here...
ben de tüyeceğim.